[
  {
    "question": "When Bush visits Dora-Rouge and Agnes in Chapter 10 of Solar Storms, she is",
    "a": "ambivalent",
    "b": "bitter",
    "c": "combative",
    "d": "excited",
    "e": "distracted",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many 'human territories' separate Adam's Rib and the land of the Fat-Eaters?",
    "a": "three",
    "b": "six",
    "c": "five",
    "d": "four",
    "e": "two",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Chapter 10 of Solar Storms, why is Angel surprised when Bush reveals her full plan?",
    "a": "Spring is a bad time to travel.",
    "b": "Bush wants LaRue to drive the group north.",
    "c": "Bush plans to take Dora-Rouge with them.",
    "d": "The money for selling shirts has gone to a new canoe.",
    "e": "Bush plans to travel over land rather than water.",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following objects does Dora-Rouge claim are 'only masks over the face of God'?",
    "a": "forests",
    "b": "lakes",
    "c": "maps",
    "d": "scars",
    "e": "dreams",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does Agnes become sad in Chapter 10 of Solar Storms?",
    "a": "She has a vision that the journey will cripple her.",
    "b": "She knows the journey north will end in her mother's death.",
    "c": "A bad spirit has put a barrier along the journey.",
    "d": "Making the journey means selling the cabin.",
    "e": "She will have to leave John Husk.",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "In lieu of Helene's body, Frenchie has all of the following possessions buried EXCEPT a",
    "a": "pair of shoes",
    "b": "silver ring",
    "c": "tortoiseshell comb",
    "d": "favorite doll",
    "e": "tube of lipstick",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does Angel paddle to the Hungry Mouth at the end of Chapter 10 of Solar Storms?",
    "a": "She is following Dora-Rouge's path.",
    "b": "She looks for Helene's body.",
    "c": "She sings Helene's song where the woman died.",
    "d": "She feels the call of the void.",
    "e": "She makes an offering for safe travel.",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Chapter 11 of Solar Storms, Bush buys all of the following items EXCEPT",
    "a": "meat",
    "b": "oats",
    "c": "blankets",
    "d": "boots",
    "e": "milk",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is MOST optimistic about the journey north during Chapter 11 of Solar Storms?",
    "a": "John Husk",
    "b": "Agnes",
    "c": "Bush",
    "d": "Dora-Rouge",
    "e": "Tommy",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "How old is the wine Dora-Rouge gives to Frenchie in Chapter 11 of Solar Storms?",
    "a": "50 years old",
    "b": "10 years old",
    "c": "100 years old",
    "d": "25 years old",
    "e": "5 years old",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Chapter 11 of Solar Storms, Angel compares herself to flowers grown in",
    "a": "Canada",
    "b": "Adam's Rib",
    "c": "Oklahoma",
    "d": "a greenhouse",
    "e": "a backyard garden",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "At the farewell party in Chapter 11 of Solar Storms, Angel must deal with",
    "a": "harassment",
    "b": "leg cramps",
    "c": "insults",
    "d": "migraines",
    "e": "unwanted advice",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "After Justin offends Frenchie with his political comments, how does he try to save face?",
    "a": "going back to his poker buddies",
    "b": "promising her luxuries",
    "c": "doubling down on his position",
    "d": "blaming his time in the Army",
    "e": "taking back his engagement ring",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Chapter 11 of Solar Storms, Dora-Rouge frets that John Husk will damage her",
    "a": "teeth",
    "b": "kidneys",
    "c": "liver",
    "d": "stomach",
    "e": "eyes",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does Agnes almost turn back on the first day of the journey north in Solar Storms?",
    "a": "A bear sighting is a poor omen.",
    "b": "The fear of losing her mother is too much.",
    "c": "She has forgotten her coat.",
    "d": "Dora-Rouge becomes ill.",
    "e": "One of the canoes has sprung a leak.",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Chapter 11 of Solar Storms, why does Angel not eat the fried chicken on the first night of the journey?",
    "a": "She drops it into the lake.",
    "b": "She falls asleep before supper.",
    "c": "She listens to Dora-Rouge and her warning against it.",
    "d": "She has adopted a vow of vegetarianism.",
    "e": "She thinks it looks diseased.",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did Dora-Rouge wear sunglasses while fleeing the boarding school?",
    "a": "She was guarding against snow blindness.",
    "b": "She was hiding a black eye.",
    "c": "She was ashamed of her brown eyes.",
    "d": "She was taking revenge against a man she hated.",
    "e": "She was trying to disguise her identity.",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Chapter 11 of Solar Storms, when the travelers are in their mosquito gear, Angel compares their looks to",
    "a": "faces behind screen doors",
    "b": "animals in nets",
    "c": "mourners at a funeral",
    "d": "brides on safari",
    "e": "mummies in a museum",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to Agnes in Chapter 11 of Solar Storms, Angel attracts mosquitoes because she",
    "a": "broods too much",
    "b": "cannot stay still",
    "c": "eats sugar",
    "d": "disrespects Dora-Rouge",
    "e": "acts like a man",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "On the drowned island in Chapter 11 of Solar Storms, which of the following animals appears when the rock painting wall is wet?",
    "a": "moose",
    "b": "deer",
    "c": "fish",
    "d": "bird",
    "e": "wolverine",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to Bush, why did her uncle survive his encounter with the thirty bears?",
    "a": "The uncle found a tree too tall for them to climb.",
    "b": "The uncle disguised himself as a bear.",
    "c": "The uncle found a cave the bears did not know.",
    "d": "The bears, in their majesty, overlooked the uncle.",
    "e": "The bears treated him as a helpless cub.",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the author foreshadow navigation difficulties in Chapter 11 of Solar Storms?",
    "a": "The drowned island puts them off course.",
    "b": "Agnes forgets her bear coat.",
    "c": "Bush’s paper map falls apart.",
    "d": "A centuries-old beaver dam is found broken.",
    "e": "Dora-Rouge’s sense of direction fails her.",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dora-Rouge claims that the ninth day of creation gave rise to",
    "a": "roaches",
    "b": "thieves",
    "c": "war",
    "d": "stories",
    "e": "harmony",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does the canoeist Bob think he is lost in Chapter 11 of Solar Storms?",
    "a": "He thinks that he studied the wrong maps.",
    "b": "The plane put him down in the wrong place.",
    "c": "A storm broke off an ancient tree.",
    "d": "Damming the rivers has altered the waterways.",
    "e": "An ancient ruin has been torn down.",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following makeup items does Angel crave after seeing Bob and Jean for the first time?",
    "a": "eye shadow",
    "b": "foundation",
    "c": "mascara",
    "d": "lipstick",
    "e": "blush",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Chapter 11 of Solar Storms, which of the following rivers does Bob say was diverted into the Se Nay River?",
    "a": "Moson Khani River",
    "b": "Wente Mapu River",
    "c": "Big Arm River",
    "d": "Deer Head River",
    "e": "Strong Hand River",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Chapter 11 of Solar Storms, Agnes claims that Bob and Jean are",
    "a": "thieves",
    "b": "demons",
    "c": "fugitives",
    "d": "murderers",
    "e": "cannibals",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Chapter 11 of Solar Storms, Dora-Rouge saying, 'Those women are plumb crazy' tells the reader that",
    "a": "she is receding further into dementia",
    "b": "her dreams copy others’ speech",
    "c": "she remembers LaRue’s insult back at Adam’s Rib",
    "d": "her bond with her family is weakening",
    "e": "she was awake in the night",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to a story in Chapter 11 of Solar Storms, the mother of war and starvation traveled in a boat made of",
    "a": "river ice",
    "b": "animal bones",
    "c": "iron blades",
    "d": "burnt wood",
    "e": "human skin",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Chapter 11 of Solar Storms, Agnes expresses a wish to have her body",
    "a": "left to animals",
    "b": "buried",
    "c": "cremated",
    "d": "hid in a cave",
    "e": "submerged in a lake",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  }
]